Talented Software Engineer has professional experience over two and half year who graduated from Computer Engineering, Detail-oriented and molivated to stay on task, meet timelines and accomplish goals. Strong analytical and arganizational skills within Web Development Industry, Pluent In Java, Co and JavascriptTypescript programming languages used to develop software within Profited and Bockend, Complex problem-solver with analytical and driven mindset. Proud team player focused on activiting project objectives with accuracy.

Work History

2023-09 - Current

Freelance Fullstack Software Engineer

- set-confracted

 Mostly dealing with Golang and Node is backend endpoints.

 Working on database design problems especially for clients who asks scalable and as simple as possible app.

 Touching some frontend problems (React CSR)

 Exercising an overletal (self-curiosity)

 Researching about AI especially implementations on web technologies.

2023-01 - 2023-07

Full-stack Software Engineer

- retrogi Company

 Designed and implemented scalable application programming interfaces.

 Consulted about JVMLJava Virtual Machine), Java web trameworks like spring/spring Boot. Open and Java. Scala.Go.Javascrip1/typescrip1 programming languages.

 Adopted engineering best practices and delivered highest quality scalable solutions.

- Adopted engineering best practices and delivered highest quarry scuause solutions.
 Proted with fellow engineers to brainstorm ideas, debug problems and review code.
 Gained experience about system architect, how to develop scaled performant applications using mondlift (vertical scale) and microservice (horizontal scale) architectures.
 Performed development, debugging, optimization and automation to support implementation or products and applications.
 Gained experience about database technologies such as MySQL, PostgreSQL as SQL Cossandra, Reds. Mongooble as NoSQL.
 Gained experience about CirCD (Cloud Integration and Development) like GillHub Actions. Circle Cl and Jenkins
 Gained experience about cloud computing platforms, especially AWS/Amazon Web Services).

2021-07 - 2022-12

Junior Software Engineer

- Junior Software Engineer

 Rerogi Company

 Worked to improve Herogi that makes automated workflows for fast moving customer data.

 Worked no how to decide large citent side application's software architecture. Gesigning backered Api, creating database queries etc..

 Consolled with engineering team to determine how to develop improvement of the control of

2021-01 - 2021-06

Software Engineering Intern

- Collaborated with software engineers to develop and test applicat rocedures for system efficiency, repared and submitted reports and other documentation to assist

- Prepared and submitted reports and united accessors and an advantage development from members.
 Demonstrated filme management, organizational, prioritization, and planning skills by successfully handling lasks, projects and priorities.
 Worked on mostly modern web development. Technologies like Himl. Css and libraries, Javascript. Typescript and functional programming.

2019-02 - 2019-03

IT Software Engineer Intern

- Eczacibaşı , Esklşehir

 Supported student learning objectives through personalized and sm
 assistance.

- asistance.

 Working will internal and external network devices setup and configuration.

 Activeved desistop app by designing and implementing database connected data formatting app project during internship.

 Used SAP to achieve paper documents electronically, increasing usability and office organization.

Education 2016-09 - 2021-06

2011-09 - 2015-07

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

High School Diploma

ir Anatolia Teacher High School - Kırşehir Turkey

Languages

TOTAL	Exceller
English	Very Goo
	Voly 000

Skills

Go JavaScript / TypeScript

React / React Native

Spring / Spring Boot
System Architecture / Scalable Apps
Database Management and Technologies

Client presentation

Programming Life Cycles / Agile-Scrum Flexible and Adaptable

eamwork and Collaboro

Interpersonal Communication

Active Listenina

Certifications

Udemy - Javascript-advanced

Udemy - Spring-framework5-beginner-to-guru

Udemy - Spring Boot Microservices with Spring Cloud Beginner to Guru

Udemy - Sifirdan React ve Context Api Udemy - Devops Fundementals - CI/CD with AWS+Docker+Jenkins

Udemy - Scala Functional Programming Essentials

Youtube, Stackoverflow and other platforms resources

Udemy Golang Complete Developer's Guide

Self Projects

- Swelfekil e-commerce frontend willh SSR
 Golang e-commerce monolith backend with Postgres Nosql
 Spring Boot monolith to microservice Chat App Full-Stack
 Spring Boot monolith Biog App Backend
 Spring Boot microservice Biog App Backend
 Spring Boot Event Tickel Generator Monolith Backend
 React-Redux Event Tickel Generator frontend
 Java Swing Secure Password Store Generator
 Go Simple Notebook Cil CSV store
 Go-Simple Notebook Cil CSV store
 Go-Fiber monolith Biog App Backend
 Fiebase Simple Chat App Backend
 React-Redux Simple Chat App Frontend
 React-Redux Simple Chat App Frontend
 JSC carrvas multiplayer Agardo like garne

Accomplishments

Tubitak 2209-A University Students Research Projects Support Program 2020. Our project name Emotion Recognition by Thermal Camera has been supported.